♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and
his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in
an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman ♪
♪ Whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal who wants
to rule the world ♪
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse ♪
♪ And in a rocket ship she hunts
him all across the universe ♪
- I'll get you.
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
- You're on.
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Oh my stars.
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- Check me out.
- Crow
- I'm different.
♪ If you wonder how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar music)
(door creaking)
- Hi everyone, Mike Nelson
here on Satellite of Love.
We're--
(engine revving)
- Hey man.
- Oh hey Servo.
- What, are you saying
I'm short, what?
- No, I was gonna ask
where you've been.
- Oh, well I had karate, then
I swung by the gym to lift.
'Cause I had some extra
time before picking up
my hot new girlfriend, Kristy,
who will most likely
wear her thong
as she clings to me on
the back of my Harley.
Yeah, we're gonna make
out in public a little.
- Servo, you look different.
Hey, you've got lifts in
your hover skirt don't you?
- Hey man, watch what
you're saying there, man.
- (laughs) You do, you have
lifts in your hover skirt.
- All right, that's it.
- Hey, hey, take it easy.
- Easy, easy.
- Take it easy.
Tom, I'm afraid you've
got short man's disease.
- What?
- Okay, it's the tendency
for height-challenged males
to overcompensate for a
perceived lack of machismo.
- So what, are you
saying I'm short, huh?
- Yeah, I'm afraid
that is implicit.
- Oh man.
- No problem though.
We just rub a little
baby aspirin on your gums
and you'll be fine.
(Tom spitting)
(Tom crying)
- There, there, that's better.
We'll be right back.
- Can I keep my nunchucks?
- We'll see, honey.
- Violent shrimp.
(Tom crying)
- Little baby short
man, we'll see.
(upbeat music)
Well, how's your courageous
battle with short man's disease?
- I'm over that.
Turns out I'm not
even short. (laughs)
- Right.
Well, how about
your face, Servo?
Does your face hurt?
- No, why?
- 'Cause it's killing me!
(laughing)
- Really?
Oh geez, I'm sorry Crow.
I'll have that
checked right away.
- Oh never mind.
- Oh, I had no idea.
- Let's see what
Pearl and them want.
- Just ruin my
joke why don't you.
- How nice to see you Nelkirk.
I only have a moment.
I'm expecting
everyone for the ball.
Isn't it marvelous?
Everyone, simply everyone
is invited to my ball,
except let's see, except
Michael J. Nelson,
Crow T. Robot, Gypsy,
and a Tim Servo.
I'm dreadfully sorry, there
just wasn't enough room,
and this is my first ball.
Why, the walls of
this castle barely hum
with the unearthly
presence of parties past.
Listen.
(chewing)
- (laughs) I'm
telling you law giver,
these cannapes are
flying out of here.
I can barely keep
up with myself.
- Well anyway, this
ball shall celebrate
the triumphant
return of a forester
to this dwelling of evil.
- Well that sounds great, Pearl.
Hope your party's a big success.
When does the ball start?
- Oh, in about two
and a half hours ago.
Okay, I'm gonna need
you guys to pretend
like you're part of the party.
I think that will really draw
in the rest of the guests.
So come on, mingle, make it
look like you're having fun.
(laughing)
- What a marvelous anecdote.
So, how do you know Pearl?
- Well, she's got me
trapped up here actually.
- Really?
How awful for you.
- Say Mike, are you
gonna introduce me
to your purple friend here?
- Don't you dare, Nelson.
- Oh I say everyone, everyone,
let's play charades in
the parlor. (laughs)
- Oh baby, why you gots to go?
♪ Cheese, glorious cheese ♪
- Oh forget it.
You couldn't mingle your
way out of a wet paper bag
if it was--
♪ The greater love ♪
- Brain guy.
- What?
- You must get
ready for the ball.
It might be gonna start soon.
- Thanks anyway, Pearl, but
I'm just gonna stay in tonight.
(doorbell ringing)
- It worked!
Everyone, they're
here, everyone.
- This way, Ortega.
I invited Ortega over tonight
to watch Sliders in my room.
We won't get in your way.
(Ortega mumbling)
(laughing)
- Oh, thank you Ortega.
You look gravishing too.
- Oh right this way, you guys.
This is Ortega's cousin, Stacy,
and her boyfriend, Brian.
This is Pearl.
(hands clapping) So anyway,
we won't get in your hair.
C'mon you guys.
Brian, how's it hanging?
- Yeah, I hope we won't
disturb you with all the fun
we'll be having.
(door creaking)
Okay you kids, you're
gonna watch a movie
while Pearl has company.
It's "Pumaman" and
no coming downstairs
during Pearl's party.
- Oh by the way, Pearl, if
anyone else should happen
to swing by, just point
them back to my room.
Thanks a lot.
- Of course.
- (mumbles) I'm eating
these things faster
than I can turn
them out. (laughs)
Ooh, Junior Mint.
(laughing)
- Oh crap, I got bean dip
all over my new silk organza
tool strap--
(alarm buzzing)
- Oh now we got a movie.
What else can go wrong?
(alarm buzzing)
(door thudding)
(water dripping)
(system beeping)
(door creaking)
- [Tom] Ow, my corset
is fighting me.
Who gave themself
such a peppy name?
(Mike laughing)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh okay,
okay, listen you guys.
An ancient Aztec legend
tells of a God, (laughs)
who descended to
Earth from the stars--
- [Mike] Oh, you know what?
I've heard this, so I'll
just stop you there.
It's a good one though.
- [Crow] Nevermind.
- [Tom] It's funny.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Wow, the aliens really
cherried out their spaceship.
- [Tom] Christmas
ornaments of the Gods.
- [Mike] Hot bathosphere action.
- [Crow] No one
knows who they were
or what they were doing.
- [Narrator] I speak
to all humanity.
- [Mike] Can you
hear me in the back?
- [Narrator] With this mask,
I will always be with you.
- [Tom] Oh that'll be fun.
- [Narrator] My son
will be its custodian,
as will be the sons of his sons.
- [Crow] Well, gotta go.
- [Narrator] Through the ages,
he will have the
powers of a man god.
The powers of a Pumaman.
- [Mike] And the
power of bleach.
- [Narrator] The Pumaman--
- [Tom] Does that sound right?
- [Narrator] The Pumaman.
- [Tom] I think that's
what I mean to say.
- [Narrator] The Pumaman.
- [Tom] Now it
just sounds funny.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Well there's a
couple of Aztec names for you.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh, the Pumaman.
- [Crow] Copyright 1462?
What is that?
- [Mike] (laughs) I
think you need to study
your roman numerals.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Tonight, on a very
special touched by a Pumaman.
- [Crow] Now, the little hand
towels are for our guest star.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh, a bunch of hairy
guys in thongs sat down
and wrote a screenplay.
- [Mike] With Randall
Text Cobb as the mask.
- [Tom] Oh, he's the
consigliere of this film.
- [Crow] And Pizon or
Michael Billingsly.
- [Mike] At least this
movie will have nice shoes.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Back, back,
back, it's a home run!
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Well, someone
seems to have gilded you,
and that's what causing
your skin problems.
- [Mike] I can't help but feel
that you're staring at me.
- [Tom] Die, Ann, die.
- [Crow] There's something
wrong with this mirror.
- [Kobras] Well Jane.
- [Tom] Are you getting serious?
- [Kobras] Do you think
you can decipher it?
- [Mike] If you need your
toast buttered, ma'am,
I'm your man.
- Yes, it's an Aztec
inscription about a man
with the blood of
a god in his veins
who comes from outer space.
- [Tom] Georgette Relic Hunter.
- A Pumaman.
- [Mike] I guess
what I meant was,
"Are you gonna type
those letters?"
- [Crow] I also serve as
a napkin holder, ma'am,
if you need that.
(dramatic music)
- Please, continue.
- [Tom] It's fascinating.
- It's a curse.
- [Mike] It says the F word.
- [Crow] Are they all
trying to make weight?
- Whoever desecrates
the Puma god image
will in turn be destroyed
by the living Pumaman.
- That's ridiculous.
It's just a legend.
- [Tom] I'm confused.
Now I'm happy.
- Sometimes there is more truth
in legends than in history.
- [Mike] And there's more
salt in ham than in turkey.
- So, the curse
can strike you too.
- I always prefer
to strike first.
- [Crow] Oh I hope that
striking first thing
works out real good for you.
- [Tom] Oh idol's
got a fanny pack.
(statue clinking)
(door snapping)
- [Mike] Intel inside.
♪ Dun dun doo dink ♪
- Incredible!
A 3,000 year old find.
- [Tom] Oh boy.
- It conceals
unthinkable technology.
- [Crow] We gotta
hire a brunette.
(door snapping)
- But this is proof of
an outer space presence
in our history.
- [Tom] She said
that about waffles.
- It's an incredible discovery.
- [Mike] An egg, oh
it's Donald Pleasence.
- We must inform the press.
- That is not for you to decide.
- [Crow] That's Cheryl
Ladd's department.
- You can't hide this.
- Who is to prevent me?
- [Tom] A halfway smart
guy with muscles and hair.
(Mike laughing)
- Miss Dobson.
- [Tom] Could you
gift wrap this for us?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hit me with
your best slap shot.
- Your mind.
- [Tom] Oh, did you put
an aspirin in my Coke?
- And your will.
- [Mike] Oh, they control
the will game again.
- Belong to me.
- [Crow] I have a receipt.
- [Man] Forever.
- [Tom] I think controlling
your will might involve
slow gin and a Trans Am.
- [Mike] Uh-oh, hey,
oh did somebody put
unleaded in this thing?
(wind blowing)
- [Crow] Yeah, this
is what it's like
when I put my contacts
on inside out.
(books slamming)
- [Tom] Hey, telekinetic
book dumping.
- Go now and obey.
- [Mike] Get me a soda
pop and a Caramello.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] It's S&M day
at the Field Museum.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh let me
try, let me try.
(dramatic music)
Who did we get this from?
Is there a card with this?
- [Crow] Oh is halftime over?
What's the score over there?
(ominous music)
- [Tom] I'm a supermodel
of Christmas past.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] He's
basically an old baby.
(ominous music)
- We make slaves of
men with this mask.
- [Crow] And we'll
rule fish too.
- We'll dominate the world.
Who can stop us?
- [Tom] With my brains
and your beauty.
- The Pumaman.
- [Mike] Pumaman.
- We must find him.
- [Crow] Then we'll
lock him in a pet taxi.
- And kill him.
- [Tom] I'll send him a
cease and desist letter.
(suspenseful music)
(screaming)
(yells) Hey look,
Big Ben. (yells)
(glass shattering)
We're downsizing, Steve.
(camera clicking)
It's a great game
of slumming special.
(intense music)
- [Crow] Call our
900 number and vote.
(mellow music)
- [Mike] The new Big
Bird action wear.
- [Tom] I'm supposed
to be in biolab.
Man, how much
patchouli do you need?
- [Crow] Ted Cassidy in his
most sensitive role yet.
- [Tom] Doo do boon bo doo.
He's got a great butt.
- [Mike] This is where Cher
stores her discarded ribs.
- Mr. Farms.
- [Crow] I'm Bernie Capelle.
- Yes, sir, I know.
I mustn't mistake
this museum for a gym.
- Ah, you're well
aware of that are you?
- Yes and I'm also aware
I'm not supposed to work out
during museum hours.
- [Mike] And now a
word from my sponsor.
- What's the matter?
Do you feel sick?
(dramatic music)
- No, I get this way
when I sense danger.
- [Tom] Or when I eat a
sack of White Castles.
- Well you've sensed rightly.
You're in danger of being fired.
- [Crow] I don't care,
I'll work in my uncle's
Natural History
Museum down the block.
- [Tom] You non-British guy.
(upbeat music)
Fluffy seems to be
eating less and less,
and getting thinner and thinner.
- [Crow] Who am I kidding?
I can't built a cat.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] A sweater that says,
"I've read the
works of Alan Alda."
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] I'm looking for
something in a bone,
maybe a femur, pelvis,
sack of patellas maybe.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] You're not
gonna pour molten gold
down my throat are you?
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] All right,
pencils down, class.
- [Crow] The dry
look from Gillette.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Uh-oh, shoplifting
a hip bone for his grandma.
Here he goes.
- [Crow] Yeah, this
is why 7-Elevens allow
no more than three
Aztecs at one time.
- [Mike] I'm gonna
tell Mr. Weatherby.
- [Tom] Hey, hey,
that was my scapula.
I just took it out to air dry.
- [Crow] Now he takes
out a personal ad.
"Saw you in museum, you
took bone, I chased you."
(laughing)
- [Tom] Hey, whoop, sorry.
- [Crow] I'm fine, I
used up a perfectly good
pants wetting for that.
- [Tom] How am I ever
gonna get back in there?
This is hopeless, I
should just go home.
- [Crow] Yep, he
can sense danger.
A post-it note can sense
danger better than this guy.
(dramatic music)
(laughing)
- [Mike] I'll duck into Will
Icather's ancestral home.
(door creaking)
- [Crow] Is that "If I Were
a Rich Man" on harpsichord?
- [Mike] I believe it was.
(wood crashing)
- [Tom] I'm still
not sensing danger.
(wood splitting)
- [Mike] Is this
about the pens I took?
- [Crow] You the guy that's
been writing anti-Aztec stuff
on the bathroom walls?
- [Mike] Anthony Robbins.
- You are the Pumaman.
- [Tom] Actually,
he's John Davidsonman.
- [Mike] Just gonna edge
the lawn real quick here.
- [Crow] This always happens.
People throw me out the window,
tell me I'm Pumaman, then leave.
- [Tom] (clears throat)
Hear my mighty roar, grrr.
- [Mike] I'm gonna tell
my boss I'm Pumaman.
Maybe he'll let me off early.
- [Crow] Pumaman, well I sure
hope you don't see this guy
go into heat at some point.
(Mike groaning)
Sorry.
- Professor Farms?
- [Tom] Where are the
Faye Dunaway auditions?
- Did a dinosaur get away?
- No, but he sure
looked like one.
- And you're hunting
him down with that club.
- [Crow] Look, I
don't have any change.
Leave me alone.
- Tell me, are we
meeting in a dream?
- I don't think so.
- Then it's really true.
I fell from the third floor.
- [Tom] My hair looks great.
- Aren't you hurt?
- No, just a little confused.
- [Crow] Hey, a see-through hat.
- My name's Jane Dobson and
I'd like to consult to you
about a brief thesis
on the Mesozoic era.
- Well, if you're asking
me how flying relates
to man's evolution,
I don't know.
(laughing)
- [Mike] We're a fun
couple aren't we?
- Do we have to
discuss this here?
- Is that a proposition?
- (laughs) No,
it's an invitation,
to my house tonight.
My father's having a
couple of friends over
and I was wondering
if you could join us.
I've got all my books there
and it would be easier.
This is the address.
- [Tom] Oh wait, that's
my recipe for olive loaf.
- An invitation to
the Dutch embassy?
- Does that scare you?
- Uh-huh.
- [Mike] The Dutch are mean.
- Well try to overcome it.
My father's the ambassador.
- Okay, I'll even bring
my ceremonial club.
- (laughs) Come any
way you like, but come.
- [Crow] Now that's
gotta be a proposition.
- See you tonight, nine o'clock?
- [Mike] Someone will show
you where to park the cars.
- [Tom] A zubas top with a
lab coat and a veil, it works.
- [Crow] And this is from the
missing persons collection.
- [Mike] I'm a wood sprite.
- [Crow] Is she in
mourning for her turtle?
Is that why the hat?
♪ Dum ba bum ba bum ba bum ♪
- [Mike] Mentos,
the fresh maker.
- [Crow] I've reconsidered.
I don't want you to
come to my party.
- I've contacted Tony Farms.
There's a high
probability it's him.
- Did you carry out my orders?
- Yes, sir.
He'll come to my house
for dinner tonight.
- [Tom] I don't have
to listen to that.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] We got our
paychecks in today, sir.
- Everything coincides, sir.
Looks like we found
the right man.
- Fine Ranker, I do hope so.
If only for the
sake of the others.
- [Crow] I hope to be as
bald as you someday, sir.
- [Tom] Well, we better
sponge out our outfits.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] I'm gonna say mass
if you wanna hang around.
- [Crow] Well, get over
here and pick out a wig
and let's go trick or treating.
- [Tom] Legends mobile away.
- Listen to me Dobson.
Everything is as planned
for this evening,
but there is one
slight alteration.
- [Tom] The party tray
is coming from Subway.
- I shall be at
your house by seven.
- [Tom] Why would you have a
bust of Ron Ealy in your home?
- Dismiss the servants.
I don't want any
strangers interfering.
- [Crow] It's kind
of a noticeable tick.
(gulping)
- [Mike] Parachute/bow tie.
- [Tom] Damn clapper, geez.
- [Crow] David Bernie is the
Aramisman in Wait Until Dark.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] There's cherry
Kool-Aid in my saline bottle.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Wanna see the pictures?
Your boudoir shots
turned out great.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] I'm gonna
plunger him senseless.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] No one interrupts
my prom preparations.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Every room in this
hotel comes with an Aztec.
- You see in the dark.
You fall like a cat.
You are the Pumaman.
- No, I'm a mad man and
I'll smash your head in
if you take one more step.
- Pumaman does not
kill my people.
- He doesn't, but I
do, now get outta here.
- You can chase me away, but
not the blood in your veins.
Your father saw in the dark.
Your father jumped in the air.
Your father protected my people.
- My father was a physician.
The only he protected
were his patients.
- A doctor here, but a great
Pumaman in the Andes plateau.
- [Tom] Oh yeah, he
was for a couple years.
- You're a crazy criminal,
but this is the last time
you go around throwing
people out of windows.
- Before you call the police--
- [Crow] Caress.
- Look.
- [Mike] I'm a representative
of Aztechnologies.
- [Tom] Definitive proof that
he has a copy of that picture.
- [Vadinho] You were
only a boy at the time.
- [Crow] Then you were a girl
and then you were a boy again.
- I did not need to
kill to find you.
- [Mike] I kill for fun.
- Who are you anyway?
- My name is Vadinho.
- [Crow] I'm an onion.
- I'm the high priest
of the temple of the god
who came from other worlds.
- What do you want from me?
- I came to give you this.
- [Tom] Whoa, hey.
- It belonged to your father.
With this, you will have
all the powers he did.
- [Mike] Or your money back.
- I will teach you to use them.
Put it on.
- You're nuts.
- I said put it on.
- The hell with putting it on.
Can you imagine me
showing up at the Dobson's
wearing something like that?
- [Crow] Look what you're
wearing now, I mean.
- I say put it on.
- [Mike] And you say put it on.
- And you put it on.
- Okay, pal, okay, take it easy.
- [Tom] I hate it when
Aztecs force themselves
into your hotel room and
make you try on belts.
- [Mike] Nothing worse.
(light clicking)
- [Crow] Wow, look at all
the Farrah Fawcett posters.
(laughing)
- Hey, where's your phone?
I wanna check my
Aztech messages.
(door slamming)
(door creaking)
Come in Nannites.
- Hey Spike, what are you doing?
- Oh I gotta get a hair
appointment with the Nannites.
Thinking of getting
that dry look
like the guy in the Puma movie.
- Mike, your sense of style,
as always, is unerring.
Go for it, you turkey.
- Hi, can I help you?
- Oh well yeah, I had a
hair appointment for now.
- Oh hi Mike.
Are we gonna do the
same as last time or?
- Ooh, well hi Shelly.
No offense, but last time you
made my hair 70 miles high.
So I was wondering if
any of the other stylists
were available,
Decka or Shondelle.
- Oh, I see, I understand.
- Great 'cause I don't mean to--
- They're all busy, I just
checked, it's just me.
Now what do you want?
- Well, if I could
get the dry look,
if it's not too much trouble.
- Trouble, why would
it be any trouble?
It's no trouble at all.
So, you got the day off today,
or you live around here,
or is it pretty nice out today?
There, you're
done, the dry look.
- Well, thanks Shelly.
I hope I didn't offend you.
Ooh, so sensitive, man.
- Mike, I think she might've
went just a little too dry.
- What are you talking about?
I'm sure it's, ow, ooh.
Well, maybe she went a
little heavy on the mousse,
but once I shower I'm
sure it'll be fine.
We'll be right back.
- If we can just redirect
a river onto your head
I think we can salvage it.
- So you like it?
- No.
(upbeat music)
- Father, I'd like to introduce
you to Professor Farms,
the paleontologist I spoke
so much to you about.
- Welcome Professor.
- Thank you.
- [Tom] These are some old guys.
- Sir George Bradley
of the Energy Ministry,
Sir John Forbes Esquith,
Sir Michael Robinson.
- [Mike] Minister of Waffles.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Where's the keg?
- [Mike] We're here to
pick up our Grammys.
- [Tom] (clears throat) I'm
afraid I ran over your dog
in the driveway, I'm sorry.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] My name is
Pleasence and I am funky.
- [Tom] It's better
than when he wore
his little black
dress, I suppose.
- [Mike] Battle of
the network eye bags.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh no, they're
gonna start tangoing.
- [Tom] I'm sorry, this is a
no English has beens party.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] What kind of
party clown are you?
I'm not paying for this.
- [Crow] Hip Donald
room clearer Pleasence.
- [Tom] It's my irritable
bowel syndrome isn't it?
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] With Mitchum,
I can skip a day.
- [Crow] Sugar frosted eyes.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] I was supposed to
bring an appetizer wasn't I?
- [Mike] Well,
who's for foosball?
- Another one of my father's
very important friends.
- [Crow] Oh I thought
it was your aunt.
(dramatic music)
- What's the matter?
- [Tom] I'm bored.
- I don't know.
I get this way when I
sense some sort of danger.
- [Mike] Or some
sort of breasts.
- With me, what
could be dangerous?
- [Crow] Wearing
loose fitting clothing
around a power takeoff
could be dangerous.
- Your charm perhaps.
- (laughs) You're not
doing so badly yourself
for a paleontologist.
- Well, I'm from the
neanderthal school,
and occasionally my
primitive instincts pop up.
- [Tom] Wanna go and
circle a mammoth later?
- You're sounding
much better Professor.
- You make me feel like
I'm still in the museum.
Why don't you just call me Tony?
- Okay, Tony.
- [Mike] Let me show
you the way out.
Please don't come back.
- This is where I
keep all my books.
So, dinosaurs became extinct
because they no longer knew
how to love each other.
Is that correct?
- [Tom] In a wrong
kinda way, sure.
- Exactly, and I certainly
wouldn't want our species
to end the same way.
- [Crow] All aboard.
- That's the best biological
blackmail I've ever heard.
- [Tom] But Mike, this
is called kissing.
Maybe you can try this
with someone someday.
- [Mike] Well thanks, hey.
(Tom giggling)
I hate your crotch.
(hands slapping)
(groaning)
- [Tom] All right,
disco fighting.
(hands slapping)
- [Crow] He's totally
pounding Eddy Raddich.
- [Mike] Whoa.
Man, the Dutch
embassy's neighbors
must always be calling the cops.
(groaning)
(hands slapping)
- [Crow] Tiny halls for the
narrow shouldered among us.
- [Tom] Great, we're
late for tap class.
- [Mike] Ironic, he looks
like a waiter and he's dumb.
- [Crow] Al Pacino's elevator.
- [Tom] Apparently,
the house capsized
and he and Shelly Winters
have to climb up
through the basement.
- [Mike] Man, I gotta get
that order out to table six.
Why is the kitchen so
far from the dining room?
- [Crow] He's in a attic,
attic, attica, attica, attica.
- [Tom] He's gonna write
Pumaman rules on the wall.
(wood crashing)
- [Mike] Thank goodness
they made their house
out of peanut brittle.
- [Crow] So basically, a mild
rain could take out that roof.
- [Tom] My favorite
ball, I will not lose it.
- [Mike] Man, there's a lot
of reindeer crap up here.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Like an
idiot on the roof.
(Tom meowing)
- [Mike] Spends next three
hours running from edge to edge.
- Tony!
- [Crow] It's Gino, I've been
looking for you, you Mook.
- [Mike] Here, here's
a garter snake for you.
- [Crow] The world's most
persistent belt salesman.
- [Tom] There, lower
yourself down with that.
- Put it on!
- Then what?
- Jump!
- I'll be killed.
- Put it on!
- [Crow] And then get killed.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] You know what, my
mom had a pair of earrings
that did the exact same thing.
- [Crow] (laughs) No, I
mean, you look great, really.
- [Tom] Idiot.
- Jump now!
- I'm not a bird.
(upbeat music)
- [Vadinho] Fly!
(triumphant music)
- [Tom] First thing he
does is poop on my car.
(triumphant music)
- [Crow] Look out
for the, oh boy,
right into the propellers.
- [Mike] We gave him the
Captain Dork costume by mistake.
(triumphant music)
♪ Pumaman, he flies
like a moron ♪
- [Mike] He has the power to
rear project major cities.
- [Tom] Now a bird gets
sucked into his engine
and he goes down immediately.
- [Crow] Yeah, they'll
find his black box in here.
(yelling)
- [Mike] I hate to be picky,
but Pumas aren't really
known for flying.
- [Crow] I don't think so.
What, Twiggy.
- [Tom] You missed her.
- [Crow] And he immediately
uses his powers for peeping.
(triumphant music)
- Thank you, you do not abandon.
- [Mike] I kiss my
frog in your honor.
(triumphant music)
- [Crow] Snap.
- [Tom] Why don't you
give me that belt back?
I'm gonna give it
to somebody else.
- Are you convinced now?
- I don't know what's going on.
I'm afraid to move.
- You do not fly,
but your mind does.
- [Crow] Yeah thanks, Castaneda.
- You are afraid, but
the other you isn't.
- The other who?
- [Mike] Cindy Loo Hoo?
- Tell me the truth Vadinho.
Who am I?
- You have the blood of the
gods coming from other worlds.
- [Tom] Ew, god blood
is hard to get out.
- You are the Pumaman.
- It's not possible.
It's not possible.
- [Crow] We're out of Triscuits?
- Tremendous leaps.
That wasn't a man,
it was a cat jumping.
- Finally we found him.
- [Tom] Mr. Rice.
- Now the only task
is to kill him,
and that's the
easiest job of all.
- [Mike] The hardest
job is growing hair.
- [Crow] Yeah, have
another beer, honey.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Ew, I let that creepy
paleontologist kiss me.
His gooey lips are all over me.
- We're almost there.
We're about to turn around,
ready to go into action.
- [Mike] Good buddy.
- [Crow] Shake it, shake it.
Driving Donald Pleasence
around, yeah shake it.
- [Tom] Scoliosis Man here.
Check please.
- [Crow] Gods are dragging him
by the elastic in his BVDs.
- [Tom] Herbie, the
love silver shadow.
- [Mike] Pleasence and his
thugs are just spinning cookies
on a construction site.
- [Crow] Wait, the Gods got
me in a holding pattern here.
- [Tom] Oh, I sense danger.
(guns firing)
- [Mike] Are criminals
genetically drawn
to construction sites?
- [Crow] Whoa, his pants
came clean off there.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Don't lose your
footing, I mean flying power.
(gun firing)
- [Crow] I can see the same
thing only it's really red.
- [Tom] Jetsons are
flying overhead.
(gun firing)
- [Mike] Hey guys, look at
me, I'm gonna jump, watch.
Ow, my ankles.
- [Tom] It's too much mustache,
he's pushing the envelope.
- [Man] He disappeared,
we can't see him anymore.
- Idiots.
- [Mike] Get off my lap.
- Get moving, comb the
area, find him, kill him.
- [Crow] Donald's only
use for the word comb.
- [Tom] Sam Elliott
is Ted Turner in the
Gregory Peck story.
- [Mike] This is nice, I'm
gonna break out of the racket
and open a little
pie place here.
- [Crow] Yay, happy music!
- [Man] Let go of me, let go!
- I wanna know where
Kobras's hiding the mask.
- I don't know.
- Tell me or I'll drop you.
You idiot, what do you
think is gonna happen
if you shoot me?
- You'll die.
- Right, let's see what
would happen to you.
(yelling)
- [Tom] Help, I'm falling
at a 60 degree angle,
breaking all the
laws of physics.
(upbeat music)
- Are you gonna cooperate
or do you wanna end
up like the gun?
- Put me down.
- Not until you talk.
- I don't know anything.
I get my orders from Ranker.
- Where's the hideout?
- It's a secret.
- [Mike] Fall, fall.
- Only a few people know.
- And you're not
one of them, right?
Then we have nothing
to talk about.
Bye, pal.
- (yelling) I'll tell you.
- [Tom] My mustache
makes me fall sideways.
- It's in a mansion,
I swear, in a mansion,
but I don't know where.
No one who's ever been
there remembers it.
Really, everyone who
goes there doesn't talk.
- [Crow] So no one who doesn't
go there doesn't not talk?
- They can't remember anything.
They can't remember
anything, I swear, I swear.
- [Tom] Would you stop
holding me by my nipples?
(upbeat music)
- What are you doing?
Oh, don't leave me hanging here.
- [Tom] Tell me
how shot JR, c'mon.
- Come back!
- [Tom] All the gods
are snuggying me.
- [Mike] Door fun rituals.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] He landed
in a cow flop?
- It protected you?
- Yeah, he didn't help
me find out where Kobras
is hiding the mask.
It's in a mansion, that's
all I could find out.
- Fine.
- What do you mean fine?
Do you know how many
mansions there are in London?
- [Tom] Probably like a billion.
- I said fine, you can find it.
You must learn new powers.
All you do is concentrate.
- Here?
- No, we go home.
- So they can get us?
They'll be waiting there for me.
They're probably worrying
right now because I'm late,
afraid something happened to me.
- [Mike] Are pumas also
known for their whining?
- Follow me.
- [Tom] I'm gonna
kill you over here.
- [Mike] Pumaman,
Liberace with Dockers.
♪ Pumaman, when
will he find love ♪
♪ Pumaman ♪
- [Tom] Look, you call
it corn, I call it maize.
We'll never get along.
(mellow music)
- [Crow] That's where I almost
lost my virginity over there.
(mellow music)
- [Tom] High plains weenie.
- What's this supposed to be?
- My refuge.
- It fits your proportions.
- [Crow] You have a small
whiny warehouse for me?
- Is this where you sleep?
- [Tom] Did you kill a pig here?
What is this?
- How do you sleep on that?
- [Mike] Are you poor?
Ew, God.
- How one sleeps
does not matter.
How one wakes up is
important, kneel.
- [Crow] The name's
Tony actually.
- Are you sure they're up
there listening to you?
- Of course.
- And are they powerful?
- Absolutely.
- Then why don't
they give us a hand?
- They always do, only we
do not usually know it.
You know it now, kneel.
- [Tom] No, Tony, remember?
- Make silence in you.
Leave all materials
thing behind.
- [Crow] All my fabric?
- Become part of the cosmos.
- [Tom] Billions and
billions of Pumamen.
- Concentrate your mind on
the energy of the God Puma.
Have you done this, brother?
- [Mike] I'm sorry,
I wasn't listening.
- Yes.
- Good, now think hard of
that mansion, concentrate.
You will find it.
- [Crow] I can't get the pina
colada song outta my head.
- And now prepare, you
must take the great trip.
- [Mike] We're
going to grandma's?
- Dive into the nothingness.
- [Tom] Watch MTV?
- Return to the surface,
where the sacred mask is.
- How is that possible?
- Everything is
possible for the mind.
- [Crow] Well, most minds.
- Concentrate, you must
have faith in your powers,
in your heart.
- [Mike] In your
ropey little arms.
- If you want to,
you will travel, go.
(exhaling)
- [Crow] No, not
that kind of go.
(exhaling)
- [Tom] Prepare the
effeminate mobile.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
- Yes.
- Hi guys, what's up?
- You are the one, the
gods have picked you.
- You are Coatimundi Man.
- And it is time to don
your hero's costume.
Your Coatimundi look
will inspire fear
in the superstitious
criminal mind.
- Okay, well I'll
give it a whirl.
If I've been chosen and all.
- Evil beware, Coatimundi
Man is born this day.
- Okay, I'll just
put on my stuff.
You've got kinda a rhoda vest
going here it looks like,
and ooh, a Doctor Who scarf.
- Yes and with all
the attendant powers
of this majestic
Coatimundi, for instance--
- Yeah, yeah, and
for example, well--
- Well, you can shoot magnetic
laser beams from your,
from your nose, yeah, yeah.
- Yes, yes, yes, and
now he is the mighty,
yet mysterious, Coatimundi.
- His powers are yours.
It is your destiny.
- Okay, well you know what,
destiny or not, you guys,
I really had my heart set
on those cold leftover
sesame noodles.
So, I'll be your mythical
hero later, okay?
- But, but wait, don't you hear?
You're inspiring hero's
theme song is playing.
- Listen, oh and see, the
gods are coming from space
to tell you you must serve
or evil will triumphant.
- Oh wow, well I see a
beach ball and a string,
and a string and a pulley.
There's Gypsy, hey Gypsy.
- [Gypsy] Hey Mike, sorry.
- That's all right.
- She's doing the
will of the gods.
- Just pay no attention to her.
- Well you know what, hey Gyps,
I really am gonna
grab those noodles.
You wanna split them with me?
- [Gypsy] Yay, yummy, let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- There goes our God.
- Well, it would appear
that he is not yet ready
to accept his Coatimundi nature.
- Yes, and the gods are
certainly, and the gods will be.
Man, they're gonna finish
all the cold sesame noodles.
(alarm buzzing)
- Let's go, let's go.
Yeah, that's his movie sign.
- We're not gonna get any.
(alarm buzzing)
(door slamming)
(water dripping)
(door creaking)
You ate all the sesame
noodles, didn't you?
- [Mike] Yeah, they're all gone.
(dramatic music)
- Help me, father.
- [Crow] My homework
is really hard.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Excuse
me, coming through.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Bold, Mike.
- [Mike] Thanks.
- Help me, father.
- [Tom] I need a couple
of bucks to make rent.
- Help me Vadinho.
♪ Help me Vadinho ♪
♪ Help, help me Vadinho ♪
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] (sniffs) They have cats.
Oh no, that's me.
Would you take that off?
- [Crow] Look, just don't
use the holodeck anymore,
if you don't know how to use it.
- (exhales) Thank you.
- [Mike] Guy who lives
on the second floor.
- [Tom] You're pretty.
- Did you find it?
- No.
- [Crow] Then what
are you doing?
I thought you were
gonna find it.
I mean, it's okay, I just
thought you were gonna find it.
- But I learned that I
can only project myself
to a place that I know.
I have to know exactly
where I wanna go,
otherwise I'll get lost
in the nothingness.
- [Mike] So it's off to Hooters.
- Then we are no closer.
- [Tom] So you whizzed it?
- Listen Vadinho--
- [Crow] Are you
a kind of onion?
- Is finding the
mask the only way?
- Yes, if you do not succeed,
terrible things will happen.
- [Tom] The gods will
give you the wet look.
- They have lost
their connection.
- [Mike] The network is down.
- The mask is serving evil.
- Can't they do
anything from up there?
- Man is free, man
is master of himself.
- [Crow] Man sounds cool.
- But if they come,
man is no longer free.
- [Tom] And it could get pricey.
- You must concentrate.
You will find the
solution in your mind.
- [Mike] I think we saw
the limits of his mind
just a few minutes ago.
- [Crow] Let's not be
roommates anymore, okay?
- [Tom] I'm thinking of
having my chin smaller.
(upbeat music)
I'm in the fire truck
for USA up all night.
- [Crow] Soundtrack by my
little brother's Casio.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] I keep dreaming of
a little man in a tiny car.
- [Mike] Hi.
- Where did you come from?
- Out there.
- What sort of story is that?
- I'm the Pumaman.
- [Mike] Wait, who is this Guy?
- Who is he?
Somebody out of a comic strip?
I've never heard of him.
- He didn't materialize
until yesterday.
- Well are you getting
anything out of it?
- Mostly trouble.
- I told you Tony, if
you want adventure,
why don't you join up with us?
It's all the sports you can
take, high jump, low jump.
You get a free sword
at the end of it.
- I'll keep that
in mind, Martin.
But in the meantime, you
wouldn't happen to have
a transmitter and receiver
to lend me, would you?
- You mean a position indicator.
- [Crow] Hey, an
old donut back here.
- [Tom] Here's your pacemaker.
Thanks for letting me borrow it.
(transmitter beeping)
- How does it work?
- The closer you get, the
more constant the bleep.
- Over what range?
- Up to two miles.
- Okay, if you slow
down, I'll get out.
- We're here?
- No, I'm going the other way.
- What did you say you
do, the sandwich man?
- No, the Pumaman.
That's a whole different bag.
- What are you advertising?
- Men from outer space.
- [Tom] He is the Pumaman.
He can get out of a car
going three miles an hour.
Wow, the queen.
(tires squealing)
(car crashing)
- [Crow] That steering column
plunged through his
chest, that's great.
- [Tom] Lost control of
me bladder, sorry mates.
(water spraying)
- [Mike] Do you have
the jaws of life on you?
(water spraying)
(laughing)
- [Crow] I have a good mind
to join a marching band.
(laughs)
(water spraying)
- [Mike] Where am I gonna get
another personal fire truck?
(water spraying)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh I did deserve all
those beatings as a child.
(beeping)
- [Mike] Cupid.
(dramatic music)
- Here he comes.
- [Crow] Light the candles.
- [Tom] Just trying to net some
tuna and we got this thing.
- Call him.
- [Mike] He was playing
with mommy's lipstick.
(dramatic music)
- Don't come in Tony, run!
- [Crow] Eat this
baguette, eat it!
(yelling)
Grrr, grrr.
- [Mike] Stuck him in.
(groaning)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] More ketchup, please.
- Don't worry about
me, watch out!
- [Tom] He has this
trolling motor on them.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Ooh, I think he
officially bonked them.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Beat me, fine,
but to drape a net on me.
- [Mike] And then
they snagged on me,
and called me Prince Valiant,
and said I had a
stupid fakey religion.
(tires squealing)
- [Tom] Don't let them net me.
- Save yourself.
(tires squealing)
Disappear, please do it.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Do the hustle.
- [Tom] Score, it's good.
- [Crow] Into this
piece of drywall.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] He's just
doing his floor routine.
- [Man] There he is!
(gun firing)
- [Crow] Ow, ow, ow,
I'm dead, okay, ow, ow.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] The molasses.
- [Man] I don't see him anymore!
- [Man] Keep shooting anyway!
(gun firing)
- [Crow] I don't even think
he knows these guys are here.
He's just playing around.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] Weee, this is fun.
- [Mike] I love the Pumaman.
(gun firing)
- [Man] (yells) Shoot!
- [Crow] And 10 to 12 hours,
they should be out of ammo.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] My cape hock.
- [Mike] Just wanna
check your axle here.
(man yelling)
- [Man] Brakes, step on
the brakes, do something!
(man yelling)
- [Crow] Oh, so this lousy movie
ruins a perfect good Jaguar.
(gun firing)
- [Mike] Hi, what's going on?
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] The archangels wane.
(groaning)
- Tony, you have
power in your hands.
Your hands are claws.
- [Mike] Sorry, I forgot
to tell you about that.
- [Crow] Pumaman can rip
through pure contact paper.
(men yelling)
- [Man] Shoot him!
- [Mike] I am
joining your carpool.
- [Tom] These poor guys
aren't even the villains.
They just came to get some
stuff out of their You-Store-It.
- [Crow] Well, time to drop in
on the Superbowl at halftime.
- [Mike] Meanwhile,
in Georgie Girl.
- [Tom] Oh, she's driving
the camera man to school.
- [Crow] Snoopy.
(beeping)
- [Mike] Now he just pops
into old girlfriend's cars.
- Tony, how'd you get here?
- Nevermind, drive.
- [Tom] He said.
- But they'll kill
you if they find you.
Kobras wants to kill you
and they're following me.
They're right behind me.
- Nevermind, tell me
where the mask is.
- [Crow] Get your
copy at Blockbuster.
- Don't ask me that, I can't.
I swear I'd like
to, but I can't.
On condition to keep the
secret, just like everyone,
I can't do it.
- Try, fight him, fight
him with your will.
- [Mike] But my will won't.
- I can't, he's commanding
me from a distance.
- [Tom] Amelia Airhead.
- I can't do it.
Tony, help me, free me.
Something terrible's happening
to me and to everyone.
Help me, don't leave me.
- [Crow] Is that
a helmet or a hat?
- [Mike] Sorry, we
stopped for slurpees.
- There they are, run.
Run, save yourself.
- [Crow] Play your theme
music and hop around.
- [Mike] We now revisit Bride's
Head and we're revisiting.
- [Crow] It's one
of Sting's cabins.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Maybe she's visiting
Helena Bonham Carter.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Man, with those boots,
she has to use high
altitude baking directions.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Mr. McGregor's
about to shoot them.
(transmitter beeping)
- [Crow] Oh he's in DFIB,
get the crash cart stat.
(transmitter beeping)
- [Mike] This is a test of
the audience's patience.
- [Crow] I think we're
gonna sell a lot of these.
- [Tom] Hey, a raccoon.
- [Mike] Goldfinger's
riding with Octopussy.
- [Crow] I'll go mess
up and you save me.
- Meet me in the laboratory.
- [Tom] And don't ever
outdress me again.
- [Mike] Can't believe you
guys mooned us back there.
- [Crow] It's confirmed,
they brought a bundt cake.
- High ranking officers.
What the hell are
they doing here?
- [Tom] Book club.
- [Mike] Ah, my posse.
- [Crow] Let the
cookie exchange begin.
- [Tom] Wait, I don't want
to sit next to Pinoche.
- [Mike] A couple of dictators
brought dictator friends
so they had to put in the leaf.
- [Crow] Time to
plan the NATO picnic.
- Gentlemen, I'm so glad
that you considered my house
a suitable place for
this summit meeting.
- [Tom] Though I
wish you'd told me.
- I'm going to leave you
now to make your decision.
- [Mike] Who wants
what on your pizza?
- [Crow] Can you believe
what he's wearing? (whispers)
- [Tom] I hope you brought
swim trunks. (chuckles)
(door slamming)
- [Man] It seems strange
that we don't know anything
about it, it's not even on file.
- Right, besides
being a charming host,
what credentials can
this Mr. Kobras offer us?
He's unknown to our
services as well.
- That means he's
not compromised.
- [Mike] No one
else wore a cape.
- [Man] It's no matter
to elude our security.
This means he's so
smart he can do it.
- [Man] That's a distorted
way of reasoning.
- Is it distorted to us
why this summit meeting
of the heads of state
of the entire world--
- [Tom] My minky is here.
- [Man] That be held
on private property?
- It's customary to hold
this kind of meeting
and reserve in
selected locations.
Everything becomes less formal.
It's not the first time.
- But does this mansion
offer sufficient guarantees?
- [Mike] It's so great that
they wanna see my cabaret act.
- [Crow] I better get my
wiener wraps out of the oven.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] She dies her roots
black for some reason.
(machine beeping)
- [Crow] Used to have a
carny running that ride,
but the salary got too much.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] This will
take a little bit.
I'm still installing windows.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Do you guys
like North Korea?
I sure don't.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] I'll use my
powers of looking thing.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] (gasps) There's
another meeting over there.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Goldfinger
got Mike Tyson.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] The Botany 500 Man.
- [Tom] Uh-oh, they left
the meeting on too long.
- [Crow] Now we see
through a glass dumley.
- [Tom] Shimmy cocoa
pop, shimmy pop.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] They're
all agreed then.
Carrot Top is the best comic.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Yes, much better
than Yahoo Serious.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] They tried
to resell this
as a Hallmark Christmas special
when it didn't get a
theatrical release.
- [Mike] Really?
- [Tom] Yep.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Well, I'm just
gonna go get our water.
- Fine, gentlemen,
we can go home.
You will receive further
instructions at the proper time.
- [Tom] This was great, we
should do it again sometime.
Great to see you guys, let's
take the scenic road back.
(machine beeping)
- [Mike] I'm out of quarters.
- The men who control
the destiny of the
world will be here.
- [Crow] Barry Diller here?
- When the world is
mine, I alone will decide
whether it is to be war
or peace, life or death.
- [Tom] Stuffing or potatoes.
- According to the new order
which I shall establish.
- [Mike] Hey, did
the plantagenets have
a burning permit?
- [Crow] They immediately
slap Molly Hatchet
on the tape deck.
- You will never again leave
me for this irrational feeling
you call love.
I have an assignment for you.
Tony Farms is the Pumaman.
The Pumaman is my enemy.
- [Tom] Pumaman.
- Whoever is my enemy
is your enemy as well.
He must die.
- [Mike] Anyway, toes on
the line, look up a little.
- He must die and you shall
be the one to kill him.
(Tom hiccuping)
When he comes looking for
you, greet him, smile at him.
- [Tom] Buy him a beer.
- But you will be ready.
Take this gun.
- [Mike] I've got plenty, I'll
never use it, please take it.
- When he comes
near you, shoot him.
- [Tom] Can I do it tomorrow?
I've got a nail wrap scheduled.
- Kill him, finish him off.
- [Crow] Put funny
things on him.
Show people his butt.
- It will be the
greatest act of love.
- [Mike] So I'll got to
Stuart Anderson's with him
then sleep with him, got it.
- [Tom] Is this a
Glock I see before me?
- It will be an act of
love from you to me.
Do you understand me?
- [Crow] Or am I talking
to my heads here, what?
- [Mike] Hey, a statue
of Whoopie Goldberg.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Hey, Sandra
Lock's gonna take
the direct approach with Clint.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] The
slack-wearing superhero.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Now careful, you're
gonna clip one of the heads.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Love to love you, baby.
(Jane yelling)
(gun firing)
- [Mike] I can fly
two miles an hour.
- [Jane] Tony!
- [Tom] Constantly
Out of His League Man.
(force field zapping)
- [Crow] His fortress
of balditude.
- [Mike] There's Ariam,
featuring the music
of Donald Pleasence.
(Tony yelling)
- [Tom] He's the kinda
guy who'd stick his tongue
on a frozen flagpole twice.
(force field zapping)
- [Crow] Yeah, he's as
cat-like as Boog Powell.
(Tony yelling)
- [Tom] Blew a breaker, someone
must be using a toaster.
- Stop, your powers
are worn out, finished.
- [Tom] Done, completed,
shiny at the elbows.
- You cannot escape me, Pumaman.
- [Crow] Pumaman.
- [Mike] Is that right, Donald?
- You're just a small
insignificant human being.
- [Tom] A puman being.
- [Crow] I'm supposed to
come up with a snappy retort
and I can't.
- [Mike] This is where the
little elevator really pays off.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Are you leaning
on the switch over there?
(dramatic music)
Say, the door's two
steps to the right.
(wall crashing)
- [Crow] One of those
pre-fab English castles.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Puma, honey, if
you keep your legs up,
you'll go faster.
(dramatic music)
- Tony Farms.
- [Mike] Raises soybeans.
- You must obey me.
- [Crow] At all times,
he has the look of a man
who's been hit with a fish.
- I will destroy your powers.
- [Tom] Oh no, whoa, look out.
Oh Mrs. English lady, I
apologize, go backwards, okay.
(yells) Got it, I'm gonna fall.
- I will destroy your mind.
- [Crow] I will
bunch up your package
so it's very uncomfortable.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] I got a new jacket.
- You belong to me now.
- [Crow] I have the
title to your head.
(dramatic music)
- You cannot escape me.
- [Tom] Oh there go my
keys, my wallet, my condom.
(dramatic music)
- You can no longer
jump into space.
- [Mike] Look out below.
Half digested fish
and chips coming down.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Okay, okay, I
got it, whoa! (yells)
- Because you are made of Earth.
- [Crow] Corn grows in you.
- And to Earth you shall return.
- [Mike] That was an odd
thing to say, even for him.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] And there goes the
$25 million restoration
at Westminster Abbey.
(brick crashing)
- [Crow] He lost his inherent
Puma tuck pointing skills.
(Tony yelling)
- [Mike] Pumaman.
- [Tom] Look, he's
refenestrating, see.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Do the hustle.
- [Mike] If I get up there
in time, I can push him out.
- [Tom] One, oh,
(groans) Pumaman.
(upbeat music)
- Don't let yourself
go, Tony, resist!
- [Crow] Cry and fall,
is that what you said?
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Two.
Pumaman's friend.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] First save
me then change me.
- Tony Farms.
- [Tom] He has 40 acres.
- Your body no longer
belongs to you.
The forces of the cosmo
have turned you over to me.
- [Tom] Are the heads
eating potato chips?
- Come back to me!
I order you to return!
- [Mike] Mach schnell!
- I am waiting for you.
(yelling)
- [Crow] I'm back
on catnip, man.
You gotta help me.
- Help me, Vadinho!
He's calling me.
Can you hear him,
can you hear him?
I can't fight it!
- Calm yourself!
- (yells) I can't,
I'm about to go!
- [Crow] Shoe in the scenery.
- If you do, you've
lost, he'll kill you.
You must resist.
Repeat with me, each man
is a god, each man is free.
Do not think of anything
else, concentrate!
Repeat, repeat with me.
Each man is a god,
each man is free.
Each man is a god.
- Each man is a god.
- Each man is free.
- [Crow] Each man is a weenie.
- Each man is a god.
- [Vadinhoindho]
Each man is free.
- [Crow] Each man
is a puss, okay.
- [Tom] These walnuts are good.
- [Mike] Mr. Forbes is here
if you wanna go for a ride.
- I have taken away his powers.
- [Crow] So that's done anyway.
- And his will is broken,
but he's putting up
an unexpected resistance.
- I'll take care of it.
- Comb the area, find him,
but don't make any noise.
I don't want any
trouble around here.
- [Tom] If the police would
find out I'm pirating cable.
- [Mike] Break a few
more wills before lunch
then meet some death's
best on Fridays.
- Pumaman.
- [Tom] Pumaman!
- Pumaman, I am ordering you.
I am ordering you.
- [Crow] A fajita, is that okay?
- To kill yourself.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] John Boy Walton.
- [Tom] I like the
other head better.
(dramatic music)
- It's all right
Vadinho, it's over.
- [Crow] Oh great,
so can we go, Mike?
- [Mike] No.
- Listen, I want you
to hear my epitaph.
- [Mike] I'm with stupid.
- He wasn't much in his life,
either as a man or a Pumaman,
and now he's worth
absolutely nothing.
- [Crow] The same as
when he was alive.
- It's not true.
You are a worthy man.
- [Tom] Worthy of a beating.
- You will be all right.
- Only if I lose a habit.
- Which one?
- [Crow] Nose picking,
public farting?
- Wanting to live!
- [Mike] Gotta clock
these windows quick.
(hand slapping)
- [Tom] C'mon, just let me
big a big, giant baby. (cries)
- No, let me go!
- [Crow] I just
wanna help you die
with a modicum of dignity.
- When you die, you
don't suffer anymore!
You don't have a master!
- You must not die, brother.
For you, or me, or Jane, for
all who want to live free.
Listen to me.
- [Mike] Whoa.
- Perhaps there is a way.
Only 10 minutes,
but you can do it.
Go to a deep sleep, 10
minutes with no life.
It is in your power.
- [Tom] I'm just sore is all.
- Kobras does not know it.
He cannot take it from you.
- [Crow] Please get off, I'm
feeling funny down there.
- Hold your breath.
Your heartbeat can slow down.
- [Mike] You just
have to not wiggle.
- Diminish.
- [Tom] I mean, anybody
would feel this right?
It's natural, right?
- Stop.
- [Crow] So pumas are suicidally
depressive mouth breathers?
- [Mike] We show you now the
general vicinity of the heart.
- That is right, Tony.
Let yourself go.
- [Tom] Stop working out.
- You are dead.
You are dead for
all, even for Kobras.
- [Crow] Duh, okay.
(Tom humming)
♪ Tink tink tink tinkle ♪
(door slamming)
(water dripping)
- Hey, look what we made, Mike.
- Why, that looks like, why
it looks for all the world
like a replica of the
head of Roger Whitaker.
- We made it with our
genuine Aztec mask.
- Wow, that's great.
I can hear him sing right now.
♪ I left my ship
out in the harbor ♪
I assume to gain control
of his mind and his will.
- There's no other reason
I can think of to own
a replica of the head of
Roger Whitaker. (chuckles)
- Yeah exactly, but I have to
ask why, why Roger Whitaker?
Why not say, Barbara--
- Feldon, right we thought
of that, okay Mike?
And Sting, and Chipmunk,
and Senator John Warner.
- And Puff Daddy, and Al
Checky, and Web Pierce,
and Judy Carne, and
Joan Sutherland.
- And George Lindsay,
and Barbara Bush--
- And people like that, and
Mike, when you only have time
to effectively
control one person--
- We have other
things to do, Mike.
- Then Roger Whitaker
is the perfect choice.
Take our word for it.
It's who we got, now what
do you wanna do with him?
- Well, I can' think
of anything at all.
- Use your imagination,
man, it's Roger Whitaker.
I mean, that means songs, sure,
but he can probably
do other things,
light typing and filing.
Maybe you need help
with your hand washing.
- No, no I don't.
Frankly, I think
it's a waste of time.
- Oh fine, we go to
all this trouble,
hand Mike Roger Whitaker,
and he drops the ball.
- Here's the wheel,
here's the Mike.
(mumbling) What do I
do with this? (mumbles)
Now you can just go on with
your Roger Whitaker free life,
you poor sap, but the
next time you need to hear
"Durham Town," you're
on your own, good luck.
- Remember though, we
control Roger Whitaker.
- That's right.
- So watch your back!
Roger Whitaker could be
on you at any moment.
- There he is!
- Whoa!
- I'm kidding, this time.
- Yeah, look at him run.
We'll be right back everybody.
In the meantime, be on the
lookout for Roger Whitaker.
(chuckling)
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] There he
is, Roger Whitaker.
- [Mike] I'm scared.
Oh, I overdid it
on the Fancy Feast.
- [Tom] Later, Mob
Barker and the gang
come to finish him off.
- [Mike] Tee hee, tee hee.
- [Tom] They're here and the
cupcakes are still in the oven.
- [Crow] Friends are
visiting for murder.
- [Mike] Pumaman.
- [Tom] It's Cliff
Claven, hey Cliffy.
- [Crow] So let's cut
his ears and paws off.
We get the 50 buck bounty.
- [Mike] So tense right here.
- [Crow] Tell Santa I love him.
- [Mike] You won't
get my monte auto.
- He's had it.
- [Crow] Chickenpox, he
won't catch it from us.
- [Tom] So anyway, do
you have it in loading?
- We found him, he's
committed suicide.
Should I put a bullet
in him just to be sure?
- [Mike] No, that
would be cheating.
- No, it has to look like
an unfortunate accident,
but be sure that he's dead.
- You can count on it, sir.
- [Crow] Boss says I'm in charge
and I get your lunch today
and you drive.
- [Tom] Can't you
just accept it, Tom?
- [Mike] I don't know,
I just don't know.
- [Crow] Why do I have
to stay in the car?
- You couldn't find a corpse
more dead than this one.
- What are you gonna
do with the body?
- Leave him like he is.
- [Tom] Are they gone?
- [Crow] I have
slacks like that.
- [Mike] No, see this was
just really avoidable.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] I was
alive for a second.
Now I'm dead again, go away.
- Why don't you shoot him?
- Because Kobras said not to.
- [Crow] You are so
Kobras whipped, man.
- [Mike] I'm just thinking
about the last dead guy
who sprang up and
killed half our men.
- [Tom] It seems I have
you in a bit of a bind,
don't I Mr. Dead
Human? (buzzing)
- [Crow] Hate to see you
sneeze right now. (buzzing)
- [Tom] Here's the deal.
I don't make you sneeze
and you give me your Pope
for the rest of your life.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Even when dead,
his hair looks terrific.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] I just have a really
hard time making decisions,
you know, you guys?
(engine revving)
- [Mike] Pumaman.
- [Crow] No, I feel good
about our decision, I do.
No, let's go back, no forget it.
- [Tom] Certainly, this
is a victory for good.
- You succeeded, they
think you're dead,
and now they will
leave you alone.
- [Mike] To be left alone,
the goal of every great hero.
- Yeah, but what about the mask?
- Forget it, you
are only a man now.
You cannot do it.
- [Crow] Did I say man?
You're not a man, more
like a box turtle.
I'm getting out of here.
- [Tom] Do I get
to keep the cape?
- [Mike] I'm finally gonna
get my pennies counted anyway.
- And that dynamite's
for that bastard, Kobras?
- I said forget it.
- And should I also forget Jane,
and the fact that Kobras
wants to take over the world?
- [Crow] Am I supposed
to forget Jane?
- The gods have abandoned us,
or perhaps they want sacrifice.
- What sacrifice?
- My life.
- You wanna destroy Kobras
with a suicide action?
There's got to be another way.
- Kobras has the police
and all those who
command in his power.
- [Tom] A little
doobage for later.
- I must go.
- Why you?
- I am the high priest,
I'm responsible,
and if the death of
one man can save many,
that death is right.
- The death of two
men is just as right.
- [Mike] Let go of my death.
- You have no power now
and there's no reason
for you to pay.
- I have a personal reason.
- But the price is too
high, you don't come.
- Damn hard head,
stop giving orders.
I won't let you go alone.
- You are right, brother.
- [Crow] Morvel or Wilder?
- I ask you to forgive
me, but you don't come.
- Try and stop me.
- I ask you to forgive me.
- Forgive you what?
- [Mike] I've been
seeing another superhero.
- [Crow] Kaboom!
(hand slapping)
Yes, the Aztec
speaks for all of us.
- [Mike] Say hello to
the nice people, Pumaman.
- [Crow] Hello people.
- [Tom] Let me out, let me out.
You have no right to do
this, I'm the Pumaman.
- [Mike] I'll deliver
this ham, then I'll leave.
- [Crow] Oh wait,
it's back there.
- [Tom] Aztec drove to
Wisconsin, scored some M-80s.
- [Mike] Yeah.
Kids are gonna love
Easter morning.
- [Crow] Oh man, we got Aztecs.
- Hold up where you
are or I'll kill you.
- [Mike] I've got a
Member's Only jacket.
- Shoot, and everything
will blow up for a mile
in all directions.
- [Tom] Didn't have quite
the impact I was hoping.
- Tell Kobras I want
to speak to him.
- [Mike] Forget it, I'm
never gonna get through
for Yanny tickets.
- [Tom] All right, Craig
T. Nelson, make me laugh.
(static)
- [Crow] It's an Aztec
family Christmas.
- [Kobras] What do you want?
- The gold mask.
- [Mike] With your
face sweat cleaned out.
- I'm sure we could reach
some sort of agreement.
Lead him into the great hall.
Treat him like an honored guest.
I'll join you.
- [Tom] Whoa, big Aztec.
- [Crow] So what about
Montezuma, a nice guy?
(upbeat music)
- Tony's alive.
- [Mike] Don't eat saliva?
I wouldn't even think of it.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] That was an
odd series of smells.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Do the hustle.
C'mon, do the hustle.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Ooh and he put
butter under my skin,
pushed close with garlic, mmm.
- [Tom] My cat's cradle
got out of control.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] I'm going to try
to control the recycling guy
'cause I didn't sort my
stuff very good this month.
- [Crow] Do you have a great
little boys' room here?
- Step forward.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Now spin around,
let me see how those slacks
fit in the back.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Space.
- [Crow] Wow, what a strict
Department of Motor Vehicles.
(dramatic music)
- Who are you?
Why do you want the mask?
- [Tom] In order to be smoking!
- [Mike] Don't ever--
- Each man is a god.
- [Mike] Don't
ever do that again.
- Each man is free.
Each man is a god.
- [Crow] So if
each man is a god,
where does that leave
the gods, I mean?
- Each man is free.
- [Mike] He didn't ask
for your yearbook quote.
- [Vadinho] Each man is free.
- Yes, yes indeed you are free.
- Each man is free.
- You're free to obey me.
You cannot escape my
will, nor resist me.
- [Tom] Yeah, I gotta
agree with him on that one.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] I can make you wobble.
- Obey me.
- Each man is free.
- [Mike] How about guys in jail?
They're not free.
How about guys in gulags?
- Each man is free.
- [Crow] Let him go,
boss, he's so sincere.
- [Tom] I gotta
drill some eye holes
closer together in this thing.
It's so annoying.
- Each man is free.
(dramatic music)
Each man is free.
- Take those explosives
from your body.
- [Crow] Little orphan
Aztec. (chuckles)
- Don't do it!
- [Mike] He went to
the barber and said,
"Give me a haircut
like Mary Gross."
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Peek a boo, peek a boo.
- Hand them to the
person next to you.
- [Mike] On which side,
does it matter, either one?
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] At some point,
the world has gotta stop
letting idiots like this
almost take it over.
(dramatic music)
- Carefully.
- [Crow] I also got some
bottle rockets in my socks.
- That's right.
- [Mike] That's good, baby.
(yelling)
(hand slapping)
- [Crow] So basically,
the hero is this guy.
I think it's time
we face that fact.
(mirror crashing)
(dynamite exploding)
- [Mike] Oh no, the Readers
Digest condensed books.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
Whoa, Joe Theismann's
really hurt this time.
- [Tom] Man, I am
having phantom pains
like you wouldn't believe.
(dramatic music)
(wood crashing)
- [Mike] I wonder if my
girlfriend would do that for me.
(wood crashing)
- [Crow] You are
kinda weird, Mike.
(wood crashing)
- [Tom] Where's the candy?
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
- [Mike] Must run farther
away from the danger.
- [Tom] A medicine ball,
oh no, it's Donald's face.
(hand slapping)
- [Crow] Whoa, each man is
a punching bag, I guess.
- [Mike] Each man
is Jerry Corey.
♪ Everybody was Aztec fighting ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Oh great, you
know what, I've got it.
Don't worry yourself.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] A cantaloupe,
oh it's Donald.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Fernologists.
- [Crow] So, it turns into a
good old Hal Needham movie.
(Mike humming)
♪ Dick's read all
selection and service ♪
♪ Snider jog, we're
busting up prices ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] I have almost
no respect for pumas now.
I now know that if I
ever run into a puma,
I can just push
it the hell over.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] The wall
didn't bend nor they.
- [Tom] Quit playing back there.
(upbeat music)
♪ When you want the
flavor of bacon in a dip ♪
- [Mike] I wish Poaching
Protected Species Man
would show up and take
care of this thing.
- [Crow] You could
call Ted Nugent's man.
- [Tom] I can't
get out of first.
- [Mike] Take that,
members of Boston.
- [Crow] Hey Vadinho, you
gotta try this, it's fun.
(hand slapping)
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Hey, it's
Archie Rice Man.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Jump all.
♪ Believe it or not
this movie's still on ♪
♪ It should've ended
two hours ago ♪
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Is that
Donald Pleasence?
I wanna get his autograph.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Beyond Donald dome.
(wood crashing)
- [Crow] Yes, pumas have
instinctive knowledge
of wiring and home construction.
- [Tom] Grrr, I'm a deadly
puma, be frightened of me.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Didn't think he'd
sink that low. (chuckles)
- [Tom] Olly, olly, oxen free.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Okay, I'll
give him purple herm
and then a jock block.
- [Crow] Don't ever mention
Donald's jock again.
- [Mike] That's a good idea.
- [Tom] Can I borrow
a cup of bald?
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Please no, I
had a terrible childhood.
(yelling)
- [Crow] I'll herm you.
- [Tom] He's Joe Bethingham.
(force field buzzing)
- [Mike] You will drop
your pants to your ankles
and walk through town
saying, "I am a ninny."
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Make sure
you set it on bald.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Don't jiggle,
Mom wants a nice
picture for Christmas.
(dramatic music)
(force field buzzing)
- [Mike] Oh, excuse me.
- [Tom] Boy, time to call sunny
competent Aztec man again.
- [Mike] Would you look at
this beautiful hardwood floor
they covered up.
- [Crow] There's a layer
of nougat in this house.
- [Mike] I'm sensing
danger, oh it's mildew.
- [Crow] Perhaps now
would be a good time
to jump around like an idiot.
- [Tom] Castles are nice,
but they're big on
livable basement space.
- [Mike] Wool Over His Eyes Man.
- [Crow] Easily Bamboozled Man.
- [Tom] Three Steps Behind Man.
- [Mike] World, get used to
being run by Donald Pleasence.
(gun firing)
- [Crow] I guess he
sensed danger there.
- [Tom] This is flying
officer Donald Pleasence
with the traffic report.
- [Mike] Between sessions
of staring at his wigs,
he became an accomplished pilot.
- [Crow] Whoops, missed
him, better go home.
I did what I could.
- [Mike] A peach,
oh that's Donald.
(helicopter blades whirring)
- [Crow] Rest taking London.
(upbeat music)
♪ The fat free yogurt
that's not short on flavor ♪
- It's all over Kobras.
- [Crow] Ryan Timothy Kobras,
you land this
helicopter right now.
(upbeat music)
(Mike humming)
- [Tom] This is great.
Bending metal doors, no problem.
Subduing stocky senior
citizens, that's another story.
(upbeat music)
(Mike humming)
- [Crow] It got hard, bye.
(helicopter blades whirring)
(helicopter crashing)
- [Mike] Whoa, the network
shouldn't have bought
Kelsey Grammer a helicopter.
(helicopter exploding)
♪ Burning old man ♪
♪ Singe all his flesh off ♪
- [Tom] Oh then the gods
fulfilled their holy plan
to roast a man in a helicopter.
- [Mike] Thank you
Pastor Necklace.
- [Crow] Oh man, this
thing is really rank.
- [Tom] Croquet
course of the gods.
- [Mike] Hey Vadinho, would
you mind worshiping for us?
I think we're just
gonna get going.
- Evil has been defeated.
Their protection has not failed.
- [Crow] I did most of it.
- Do they also protect
couples in love?
- Respect.
Places like this were created
by them to make contact.
- [Tom] And other cold remedies.
- Kneel.
- [Mike] Look, I told
you, my name's Tony.
Man, I thought we
were getting close.
- [Tom] Man, get a room.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh holy salt lick.
- [Mike] If the space man
puma thing turns out to be
the correct religion, I for
one will be very surprised.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Yay, sky!
There's a place
where there's sky.
(triumphant music)
- [Tom] This is
indeed a blessed day.
(triumphant music)
- [Crow] It'd be fun to take
a three wheeler up there.
- [Mike] Air is pretty.
(wind blowing)
(triumphant music)
- [Tom] So these three are
the only ones stupid enough
to let the spaceman
play with them.
- [Crow] The rain's gonna
totally frizz out my hair
for our date.
- [Tom] Stonehenge is a chain?
- [Mike] Apparently.
(triumphant music)
Hi, say, did anyone see a mask?
- [Tom] Your regular god
was busy, so he sent me.
- [Crow] Yeah, it was
the second amulet kiss
that got him here.
- [Mike] Zap.
- [Tom] Sometimes, the
gods make extra money
giving people rides.
- [Crow] (laughs) You guys
took me seriously, suckers.
- [Mike] I'm just gonna
toss it on another planet
and see who bites.
- [Tom] The gods, the gods.
- [Crow] Oh crap,
it's that Aztec guy.
- [Mike] The whole bible
thing, buncha hooey.
It's all about aliens
and spinning globes.
- They are pleased
with you up there.
- [Tom] I mean, I didn't
tell them everything.
- I'm not happy
with them down here.
What's going to
happen to the mask?
- [Crow] Hey, who the hell
is that little pipsqueak?
- They are taking it
back to its temple
in the Andes mountains.
- [Mike] Where some other
villain will take it.
- And I'm going with them.
- Does that mean you're
gonna disappear too?
- [Tom] Yeah, they're
gonna whack me.
- Tell me the truth, Vadinho.
Are you one of them?
- [Crow] Me, no I'm Jewish.
- We all are a bit, but if
you want to see me again--
- [Mike] Don't.
- When you are the father
of a small Pumaman,
take him to the plateau.
- [Tom] And drop him off.
- [Vadinho] I will
teach him the powers.
- [Crow] I'll give
you a good rate
'cause you're good people.
- Goodbye, brother.
- [Mike] Goodbye, sister.
- Honor it.
- [Tom] Little titty
twister from the gods.
- Don't worry.
- Goodbye Pumaman.
- [Crow] Is there anything
I should tell the people
about truth and beauty?
- [Mike] No, I don't think so.
- [Crow] Should we
love each other--
- [Mike] No, don't
worry about it.
♪ There's only you in my life ♪
- [Crow] Keep your cat
box clean, my friend.
Watch out for urinary
tract infections, so long.
(mellow music)
- [Mike] Yeah, only the
gods could produce something
as beautiful as that.
- [Tom] If this is
all the gods can do,
I'm over to the
dark side so fast.
- [Crow] Goodbye the Pumaman,
carry on your tradition
of flying clumsily
with your rear end in the air.
- [Mike] And we hear the
doomed cry of an anal probe.
- [Tom] You know what, I
never liked your friend.
I don't want him in our wedding.
- [Crow] There's no
afterlife, sorry.
- [Mike] The bodies
of six gods were found
after their ship
crashed into a mountain
just outside London.
- Jane, tell me
it wasn't a dream.
- You can prove it
for yourself, jump.
- [Crow] Might as well, jump.
- Ready, here we go.
- [Tom] Geez, I
wouldn't trust this guy
to hold a door open for me.
(Jane laughing)
- [Crow] You've got to
fly me over to Bennigan's
so I can show Sherry.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Now I'm
going to dig my spurs
into your hindquarters.
(chuckles)
- I've never seen anybody
make love in the air.
- But that's how you
make little Pumamen.
- [Mike] Oh and he
immediately defiles
the holy gift given to him.
(upbeat music)
♪ Now they're going
to barf in the air ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Oh there's only
you in my life ♪
- [Mike] Would you stop it?
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Starring
the Gambino family
and some English guy.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Theology contained
within this picture
may not be holy accurate.
Consult your doctor before
embarking on a theology program.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] And remember to
buy Pumaman cat box filler.
Less dust, better clumping.
- [Crow] Yep, this is
music to praise the gods,
that's for sure.
(upbeat music)
♪ Glory to our space
gods in the highest ♪
♪ Warrior space gods ♪
- [Crow] Mike, this movie
just tears it for me.
I'm gonna resign.
Yeah, I quit, I'll
see you around.
- [Mike] But Crow, I don't
think you can do that.
- [Crow] I can do that.
- [Mike] It's not
over yet, Crow.
♪ And glory to the Pumamen ♪
♪ Glory to ♪
- [Mike] Would you cut that out?
♪ Is goofy as cat mask ♪
- [Mike] Stop that.
(door slamming)
(water dripping)
(door creaking)
- Roger with the car, obey.
- Well here it is.
I'm officially tendering
my resignation.
- Okay, wow it looks
very professional.
- No, stop trying to talk
me out of this, Mike.
I've made up my mind.
Who knows, maybe somewhere
out there is a guy
who's forced to watch
good movies. (chuckles)
Well, so long fellas, it's
really been a good ride.
- Okay, we'll see you then.
- Hey everyone, I'm back.
Hey, the place looks great.
Hey, how are you guys?
- Good.
- I'm freelance now and
it's really going good.
Say, any chance you have
something here for me?
- Well, right now
there's only part time
and you won't get benefits.
- Ooh, fine, fine, fine.
Whoa, I'm employed again.
Man, what a stressful
episode my life that was.
I don't know how I survived.
- I didn't even know you left.
- Hey, we better check on Pearl.
How's the ball going, Pearl?
- Ball schmall, nobody
came except Bobo
and he snapped his tether
and joined Brain Guy
and the 70 other people
who just showed up.
Just listen to that.
(people singing in background)
How is this gonna look
to my ghostly ancestors?
Isn't there anybody up there
who can give me a break
just this once?
♪ I don't believe in anymore ♪
- Could it be?
- Hello Pearl.
- Mellow folk sensation
Roger Whitaker.
How did you get here?
- Well, I sailed in and left
my ship out in the harbor.
- Oh Roger, you've
saved my ancestral ball.
- Well I'm glad too.
♪ For you are beautiful ♪
- Roger, join me
in my evil plans.
- Well I'd love to, Pearl.
♪ But tomorrow for all
the land she sailed ♪
- Yes, perfect, you
sail to England.
Contact all your henchmen,
Glen Yarborough, Pete Sieger,
the Kingston Trio.
And I will assemble an
army of aging folk singers,
and together we will lead.
Where the hell do you
think you're going?
- But Pearl, they're
singing Asia songs in there.
- One more move and
you're dead, Whitaker.
(Roger chuckles)
♪ I have no fear of death ♪
♪ It brings no sorrow ♪
- Oh yeah, fear this,
you bearded freak.
(guitar crashing)
(mellow music)
(dramatic music)
(Tony yelling)